Last night at 2:17 AM, every child from Mrs. Gandy's class woke up, got out of bed, went
downstairs, opened the front door, walked into the dark ...and they never came back.
Weapons is a horror, mystery film directed by Zach Cregger.
When all but one child from the same class mysteriously vanish on the same night at exactly the
same time, a community is left questioning who or what is behind their disappearance.
Justine, played by Julia Garner.
Archer, played by Josh Brolin.
Paul, played by Alden Ehrenreich.
James, played by Austin Abrams.
Marcus, played by Benedict Wong.
Gladys, played by Amy Madigan.
Weapons is a 2025 American mystery horror film directed,
written, produced, and co-scored by Zach Cregger.
It stars an ensemble cast including Josh Brolin, Julia Garner, Alden Ehrenreich, Austin
Abrams, Cary Christopher, Toby Huss, Benedict Wong, and Amy Madigan.
Its plot follows the case of seventeen children from the same classroom who
mysteriously run away on the same night at the same time.
After the critical and commercial success of his film Barbarian (2022),
Cregger began working on the spec script for Weapons.
It prompted a bidding war between several studios, with
New Line Cinema emerging as the victor.
The 2023 Hollywood labor disputes disrupted casting.
It initially ran from May to July 2023 before several
actors dropped out due to conflicts.
Casting resumed in February 2024 and ended in May of that year.
Filming then began in Atlanta, concluding in July.
Weapons was released in theaters in the United States
on August 8, 2025, by Warner Bros.
The film received critical acclaim, and was a box office success,
grossing $269 million against a $38 million budget.
Madigan received nominations for an Academy Award and a Golden Globe Award,
and won the Critics Choice Award for Best Supporting Actress.
The film explores themes of witch, small town,
pennsylvania, usa, ritual, junkie.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.